

CONTACT



8778587369 / 8925112898



Sriram.parthasarathy@hotmail.com



No 82 Signal Office Road Anna Nagar Pammal Chennai -600075



044 - 42088749

SKILLS

MS Word, MS Excel

PTC Creo, Autocad

LANGUAGES

English

Tamil

Hindi



HOBBIES







Sriram Parthasarathy

Articulate and accomplished admin executive experienced at keeping an office running smoothly. A communicator and collaborator who is efficient in planning, organizing, and executing meetings and conference. Comfortable with projects that require multi-tasking and flexible with changing priorities.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Mechanical Engg

Central Polytechnic College, Chennai

2015-2018

EXPERIENCE

Sify Technologies Limited

2019-Present

Tidel Park, Chennai

- Manage office supplies stock and place orders.
- Negotiated favourable terms and pricing agreements with vendors, caterers and other providers.
- Onboard vendors, write SOWs, create purchase Orders, manage invoicing.
- Coordinates between housekeeping crews to inspect assigned areas to ensure standards.
- Undertake the tasks of receiving calls, take messages and routing correspondence.
- Monitor the CCTV of all units & maintain the backup.
- To Enable the Bio-metric access & attendance for new employees.
- Prepare regular reports and presentations with statistical data, as assigned.
- Develop and carry out an efficient documentation and filing systems.
- Book Meeting rooms as required.

Saint - Gobain

2018-2019

Sriperambatur, Chennai

- Determine which machines tools, equipments, etc, will be used and where they will be stationed in the facility.
- Assess and analyze current production methods.
- Determine how many workers are needed to run the production line.

Training & Services Itd

2018 - 6 Months

Ambatur, Chennai

• Tamilnadu Skill Development Corporation conducted the test in the trade of Auto Component Assembly Fitter.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare all the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: Chennai (SRIRAM P)

Date: